<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Read aLoud</string>
    <string name="para1_grade6">Once upon a time...\n \t A farmer had a horse that had been an excellent faithful servant to him: but he was now grown too old to work; so the farmer would give him nothing more to eat, and said, \'I want you no longer, so take yourself off out of my stable; I shall not take you back again until you are stronger than a lion.\' Then he opened the door and turned him adrift. The poor horse was very melancholy, and wandered up and down in the wood, seeking some little shelter from the cold wind and rain.</string>
    <string name="para2_grade6">Presently a fox met him: \'What\'s the matter, my friend?\' said he, \'why do you hang down your head and look so lonely and woe-begone?\' \'Alas!\' replied the horse, \'justice and avarice never dwell in one house; my master has forgotten all that I have done for him so many years, and because I can no longer work he has turned me adrift, and says unless I become stronger than a lion he will not take me back again; what chance can I have of that? he knows I have none, or he would not talk so.\' However, the fox bid him be of good cheer, and said, \'I will help you; lie down there, stretch yourself out quite stiff, pretend to be dead and do not stir.\'</string>
    <string name="para3_grade6">The horse did as he was told, and the fox went straight to the lion who lived in a cave close by, and said to him, \'A little way off lies a dead horse; come with me and you may make an excellent meal of his carcase.\' The lion was greatly pleased, and set off immediately; and when they came to the horse, the fox said, \'You will not be able to eat him comfortably here; I\'ll tell you what, I will tie you fast to his tail, and then you can draw him to your den, and eat him at your leisure.\'This advice pleased the lion, so he laid himself down quietly for the fox to make him fast to the horse. But the fox managed to tie his legs together and bound all so hard and fast that with all his strength he could not set himself free.</string>
    <string name="para4_grade6">When the work was done, the fox clapped the horse on the shoulder, and said, \'Jip! Dobbin! Jip! Pull grey horse, pull!\' Then up he sprang, and moved off, dragging the lion behind him. The beast began to roar and bellow, till all the birds of the wood flew away for fright; but the horse let him sing on, and made his way quietly over the fields to his master\'s house.\'Here he is, master,\' said he, \'I have got the better of him\': and when the farmer saw his old servant, his heart relented, and he said. \'Thou shalt stay in thy stable and be well taken care of.\' And so the poor old horse had plenty to eat, and lived, till he died.</string>

    <string name="para1_grade4">Once upon a time...\n\tA peasant had a faithful horse which had grown old and could do no more work, so his master no longer wanted to give him anything to eat and said, \'I want you no longer, so go out of my stable; I shall not take you back again until you are stronger than a lion.\' The horse was sad, and went to the forest for a little protection from the weather. </string>
    <string name="para2_grade4">\tThere the fox met him and said, "Why do you hang your head so, and go about all alone? "Ah," replied the horse, "My master has forgotten what services I have performed for him for so many years, and because I can no longer plow well, he will give me no more food, and has driven me out." "Without giving you a chance?" asked the fox. "The chance was a bad one. He said, if I were still strong enough to bring him a lion, he would keep me, but he well knows that I cannot do that." The fox said, "I will help you. Just lie down, stretch out as if you were dead."</string>
    <string name="para3_grade4">\tThe horse did what the fox asked, and then the fox went to a lion and said, "A dead horse is lying out there. Just come with me, and you can have a rich meal." The lion went with him, and when they were both standing by the horse the fox said, "It is not very comfortable for you here , I will fasten it to you by the tail, and then you can drag it into your cave and eat it in peace." This advice pleased the lion. He positioned himself and kept completely quiet. But the fox tied the lion\'s legs together with the horse\'s tail, and twisted and fastened everything so well and so strongly that no amount of strength could pull it loose.</string>
    <string name="para4_grade4">\tWhen he had finished his work, he tapped the horse on the shoulder and said, "Pull, grey horse, pull!"Then up sprang the horse at once, and pulled the lion away with him. The lion began to roar so that all the birds in the forest flew up in terror, but the horse let him roar, and drew him and dragged him across the field to his master\'s door. When the master saw the lion, he was of a better mind, and said to the horse, "You shall stay with me and fare well." And he gave him plenty to eat until he died.</string>

    <string name="para1_grade2">Once upon a time...\n\tA farmer once had a loyal horse, but it had grown old and could no longer do its work. So the farmer said: "I can’t use you anymore. So away now. Out of my stable, and only come back if you can show me that you are still stronger than a lion". The poor horse was very sad, and went into the forest to get a shelter from the rain.</string>
    <string name="para2_grade2">\tIn the forest he met a fox, who said: "Why are you so sad?". The horse said, "My master has kicked me out. He told me that if I was strong enough to bring him a lion he would keep me, but he knows that is way too hard for me." The fox said: "I will help you. Just you lie down here, and stretch your legs out as if you were dead." </string>
    <string name="para3_grade2">\tThe fox went to the lion’s home and said: "There is a dead horse out there. Come and you will have a great meal." The lion went with him, and when they got to the horse, the fox said: "You can’t eat it here. I will tie the horse to you, and you can drag it to your home, and enjoy it there." The plan made the lion happy, so he stood close to the horse, and the fox tied them together. But the fox tied the lion’s legs to the horse’s tail so that it would be very hard to open it. </string>
    <string name="para4_grade2">\tWhen the fox had finished his work he said: "Pull, old horse! Pull!" Then the horse jumped up, and dragged with lion behind him. The lion roared. But the horse let him roar, and never stopped till he stood before his master’s door. When the master saw him he was very happy, and said to him: "You will stay with me, and have a good time as long as you live." </string>
    <string name="title_activity_open_screen">OpenScreenActivity</string>

</resources>
